让我们从在这个内容提供者中看一下
Let's take the look at the implementation, of an optional method,
这个可选方法的实现
we've got in the content provider.
凡是用SQLite工作过的人都知道
Anyone out there who has done work with SQLite,
将一串数据一起插入到单独的事务
knows that putting a bunch of inserts into a single transaction is
比单独插入要快得多
much faster than inserting them individually.
BulkInsert允许我们这样做
BulkInsert allows us to do that.
这个默认的实现  只是插入一串时间
The default implementation, just calls insert a bunch of times.
但是  我们可以把它在事务中打包  如果我们自己实现这个接口
But, we can wrap it in a transaction, if we implement it ourselves.
请记住我们在这里只是添加了一个天气预报事务的支持
Note that we've only added support for weather forecast transactions here,
因为这些事务是我们唯一将要插入到bulk中的
since they are the only ones we insert in bulk.
我们从调用db.beginTransaction开始
We start by calling db.beginTransaction.
循环遍历ContentValue  插入和更新
For each of the content values passed in, we insert and
我们插入的记录的数量
update the number of records inserted.
当我们完成  我们设置这个事务为成功
When we're done, we set the transaction to be successful.
然后我们靠这个最终状态来执行endTransaction
And then rely on the finally statement endTransaction.
请注意  如果我们不将这个事务设置为成功
Note, that if we do not set the transaction to be successful,
当我们调用endTransaction的时候这些记录将不会被提交
the records will not be committed when we call endTransaction.